Support for NPR Music comes from Capital
1, proud supporters of NPR Music and the
Tiny Desk Contest. What's in your
wallet? Learn more at capital1.com.
Heat. Heat.
Hey,
hey, hey.
Heat. Heat.
Hey. Hey. Hey.
Hey,
hey, hey.
Hey
hey
tonight.
Hey,
hey, hey,
hey, hey.
Heat.
Heat. Heat.
Hey, heat. Hey, heat. Heat. Heat.
Heat
up here.
Um,
just wanted to follow up on Josh's intro
to us which was very kind and thank you
and glad to be of service. Um but I just
wanted even though it's you know flee
doing this show this is really I'm just
one part of this ensemble and uh this
thing is is this I'm talking the right
way. Okay. And um this is an ensemble
that I'm a member of and um on bass uh a
few years back I wanted to get a bass
teacher because I wanted to play with
someone who was much better than me who
could teach me. And um I chose Anna
Butters
and uh
yeah
uh they are an honor to play with and
I'm very happy. Um our guitar player is
Jeff Parker and um
on drums the deepest groove on the
planet. He also makes records um under
the name Technos and he does things that
no other drummer on the planet can do
and it's beautiful. Deontony Parks
and on the keyboards on the saxophone um
the man who produced the record Honora
who was gracious enough to partner up
with me making this music and doing this
um such a virtuoso and someone that
means so much to me Josh Johnson.
Heat. Heat.
Ah,
hey.
I hear it in the air.
>> I feel it in the air.
>> Who's your neighbor? Who's your friend?
>> Ah, there's hate all around.
>> I don't care about your [__]
politics.
I don't want to hear about your
>> Oh, well, he said
>> and she said hooray.
>> Now we're human beings right here. Human
beings. We're here together.
Just one kind of people and we're here.
What you going to do? What you going to
do when it's on you?
You're scaring the kid.
The beautiful kids.
Oh yeah. They want to know. The children
want to know.
Is the ugly coming and the guns? Is the
army coming out the sun? Ah, the blood
red son. The blood red son. Oh,
then the children want to know. I'm
feeling hate all around.
It's no solution.
It's never been a solution.
Are you with me?
Build a bridge, shine a light. Build a
bridge, shine a light. Build a bridge,
shine a light. Build a bridge, shine a
light. Build a bridge, shine a light.
Build a bridge, shine a light. Mom, come
on.
>> Make something beautiful.
I don't care if it's a bad poem, if it's
a crayon scribbled on a little piece of
paper. Make something beautiful and see
somebody. Give it to somebody.
Yay.
I'm not being corny. This [__] is real.
>> Live for peace. Live for love. Live for
peace. Live for love. Live for peace.
Live for love. Live for peace. Live for
love. See the God.
See the God in everyone.
Yay.
Everyone.
Everyone
just wants to be loved.
Everyone just wants love.
See the God in everyone.
And everyone leaves out no one.
And everything besides love is
cowardice.
You want to be brave. You want to be
tough while you're [__] hard.
Peace and love is the toughest, hardest
thing you can do. Yeah, I'm angry, too.
I'm angry. The anger is easy. That [__]
is easy.
Build a bridge. It's where the courage
is. Build a bridge. It's where the
courage is. Build a bridge. It's where
the courage is.
Shine your light.
>> Thank you.
Thanks for watching. Support for NPR
music comes from Riven, makers of all
electric adventure vehicles, including
the R1S three row SUV. More at riv.com.
A quick update before you go. We're
doing another Tiny Desk giveaway. Enter
by September 12th, 2026, and you and a
friend could win a free trip to DC to
see a Tiny Desk concert live in person.
You even get to choose which upcoming
show you want to see, and it's
completely free to enter. Just go to
npr.org/ org/tinyes giveaway. Entering
is completely free, but you can get more
entries by snagging some limited edition
Tinyesk merch or by making a special
donation to the NPR network. Learn more
and enter today at npr.org/tinyes
org/inides giveaway.